module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question:'There is only ONE state with no National Park or Monument. Who is it?',
      a: 'Maryland',
      b: 'Delaware',
      c: 'Kansas',
      d: 'Missouri',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
     question:'Which National Park can only be reached by boat or plane?',
      a: 'Denali',
      b: 'Wind Cave',
      c: 'Dry Tortugas',
      d: 'American Samoa',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
     question:'Ribbon Falls in Yosemite is how many times taller than Niagra Falls?',
      a: '4',
      b: '7',
      c: '9',
      d: '15',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Some of Star Wars filmed in this park',
      a: 'White Sands',
      b: 'Redwoods',
      c: 'Zion',
      d: 'Glacier',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
     question:'Which of these parks hosts the highest point in the US',
      a: 'Denali',
      b: 'Grand Tetons',
      c: 'Rocky Mountains',
      d: 'Mount Rainier',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question:'How many National Parks are in Texas?',
      a: '1',
      b: '2',
      c: '3',
      d: '4',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
     question:'Which National Park was the location of the First Women’s Rights Convention?',
      a: 'Yellowstone',
      b: 'Chesapeake Bay',
      c: 'Saratoga Springs',
      d: 'Seneca Falls',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question:'What’s the main difference between a National Park and National Monument?',
      a: 'Monuments can be buildings',
      b: 'Size of land',
      c: 'Who proclaims them',
      d: 'All of the above',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question:'Which was the most recently designated National Park',
      a: 'Isle Royale',
      b: 'Pinnacles',
      c: 'Voyageurs',
      d: 'Mount Rainier',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question:'How many visitor centers are in the National Park System?',
      a: '342',
      b: '568',
      c: '167',
      d: '879',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
 };
 